A Guide to the Henry G. Kunkel papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA273
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ephemera, 1948-1978; 9
  - Graphic Services: photograph, slides, and negatives (Box 118)
    - Negatives: 63-3411 A-C, 1963 December 17 (Box 118, Folder 238)
    - Negatives: 63-3251, 1963 November 27 (Box 118, Folder 239)
    - Negative: 63-2358, 1963 October 28 (Box 118, Folder 240)
    - Negative: 63-1068, 1963 April 10 (Box 118, Folder 241)
    - Negative: 63-1089, 1963 April 10 (Box 118, Folder 242)
    - Negative: 64-1199, 1964 Aprill5 (Box 118, Folder 243)
    - Negative: 64-1283, 1964 April 22 (Box 118, Folder 244)
    - Negatives: 64-1314, 1964 April24 (Box 118, Folder 245)
    - Negative: 64-1433, 1964 April28 (Box 118, Folder 246)
    - Negatives: 64-1473, 1964 April30 (Box 118, Folder 247)
    - Negatives: 63-1435, 1963 May 24 (Box 118, Folder 248)
    - Negatives and Prints: 62-265B, 1963 August 26 (Box 118, Folder 249)
    - Negative: 63-0342, 1963 February 6 (Box 118, Folder 250)
    - Negative: 66-214 (Box 118, Folder 251)
    - Negative: 65-3611 (Box 118, Folder 252)
    - Negative: 65-3566 (Box 118, Folder 253)
    - Negatives: 66-1271, 1966 April 12 (Box 118, Folder 254)
    - Negative: 66-1745 (Box 118, Folder 255)
    - Negative: 65-942, 1965 March 22 (Box 118, Folder 256)
    - Negative: 66-1984, 1966 June 13 (Box 118, Folder 257)
    - Negative: 65-1166 (Box 118, Folder 258)
    - Negatives, 1966 December 15 (Box 118, Folder 259)
    - Negative: 65-1233, 1965 April 8 (Box 118, Folder 260)
    - Negative: 65-1126, 1965 April6 (Box 118, Folder 261)
  - Tapes of Clinical Rounds-Division of Protein Metabolism and Clinical Immunology (Box 119)
    - Tape 0 NB, 1977 January 5 and 12 (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Tape 4 NB, 1977 July 7, 14 (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Tape 5 NB, 1977 July 21, 28 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Tape 6 NB, 1977 August 4, 18 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Tape 7 NB, 1977 August 11, 18 (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Tape 8 NB, 1977 August 26 (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Tape 9 NB, 1977 September 8, 15 (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Tape 10 NB, 1977 September 22, 29 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Tape 11 NB (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Tape-Rounds, March 29 and April 5 (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Tape-Rounds, 1978 June 15 (Box 119, Folder 11)
      restricted from scholarly access.
    - Tape-Rounds, 1978 July 20, 27 (Box 119, Folder 12)